const qAndA = [
              {
                question: "What is the capital city?1",
                options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
                answer: "Abuja"
              },
              {
                question: "How old is the president?2",
                options: ["29", "49", "99", "76"],
                answer: "76"
              },
              {
                question: "What is the capital city?3",
                options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
                answer: "Abuja"
              },
              {
                question: "How old is the president?4",
                options: ["29", "49", "99", "76"],
                answer: "76"
              },
              {
                question: "What is the capital city?5",
                options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
                answer: "Abuja"
              },
              {
                question: "How old is the president?6",
                options: ["29", "49", "99", "76"],
                answer: "76"
              },
              {
                question: "What is the capital city?7",
                options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
                answer: "Abuja"
              },
              {
                question: "How old is the president?8",
                options: ["29", "49", "99", "76"],
                answer: "76"
              },
              {
                question: "What is the capital city?9",
                options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
                answer: "Abuja"
              },
              {
                question: "How old is the president?10",
                options: ["29", "49", "99", "76"],
                answer: "76"
              }
            ]